Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hi! I'm Dick Donner.
Or as they would like me to say.
Richard Donner.
Of course. it's a Richard Donner film.
but--
Dick. My friends call me Dick.
I consider everybody out there
a friend...
...because you people asked for and
waited to see my version of Superman II.
But if you hadn't asked.
and requested it...
...I don't think it would've seen
the light of day.
And I thought it would lay in the vaults
of Europe and never surface again.
But because of all your requests
and all your asking it came to be.
But over the past three decades...
...much has happened.
Most of all. I got gray hair
I didn't have when I started.
But much of my film had been lost.
And it was. as I said. in vaults and
misplaced. as films happen to be.
And a lot of it was ruined.
But through really good research
and hard work...
...every bit was found that I had shot.
But some of the film you're gonna see
in Superman II. I didn't shoot.
The producers felt they wanted to
bring another director in...
...and so he shot some of the film
you're going to see.
Nonetheless. here's Superman II with as
much of my work as could be salvaged.
So thanks to Warner Bros..
thanks to all of you people
for making all this possible.
and thank you. Michael Thau.
for reconstructing my film...
...as close to the original version
as I intended it to be.
I just got a kick out of seeing it.
something I never thought would happen.
It was quite emotional; quite exciting.
Thirty years. I hope you all enjoy it.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm